http://www.villagetaways.com/privacy-policy

Choose your next getaway
Australia (495)
North Queensland (67)Byron Bay (114)Victoria (2)Western Australia (3)Sydney Nth Beaches (81)Sydney (144)Port Stephens (1)Tasmania (1)Gold Coast (18)Noosa (60)Melbourne (2)Southern NSW Coast & Highlands (2)
Bali (538)
Legian (11)Seminyak (121)Umalas (32)Canggu (142)Jimbaran (15)Uluwatu (64)Nusa Dua (15)Sanur (26)Ubud (40)Tabanan (10)Lombok (6)Tanah Lot (10)Batubelig (21)Lovina (2)Candidasa (11)Kerobokan (7)The Bukit (2)Klungkung (1)Nusa Lembongan (2)
Thailand (478)
Phuket (286)Koh Samui (162)Chiang Mai (10)Krabi (12)Hua Hin (2)Koh Phangan (1)Pattaya (3)Koh Chang (1)Chiang Rai (1)
Caribbean (36)
Anguilla (4)Bahamas (1)St Barts (4)St Martin (3)Jamaica (8)British Virgin Islands (7)Barbados (4)Turks & Caicos (2)St Thomas (1)St. John (2)
Costa Rica (20)
Nicoya Peninsula (6)The Dominical Area
(2)Las Olas (12)
Croatia (6)
Croatia (1)Brac (3)Dubrovnik (1)Split (1)
Fiji (19)
Fiji Islands (3)Viti Levu - Main Island (3)Vomo Island (6)Taveuni (1)Malolo Lailai Island (1)Wadiji Island (1)Vanua Levu (3)Viti Levu (1)
For Sale (1)
New Zealand (1)
France (103)
St. Tropez (75)Cap Ferrat (1)Corsica (1)Provence (4)Cap D Antibes (1)Paris (4)Loire Valley (1)Cannes (3)Mougins (7)Gers (1)Biarritz (1)St. Maxime (1)Saint-Raphaël (2)Alpes Maritimes (1)
Greece (20)
Mykonos (11)Andros (1)Sifnos (2)Paros (2)Porto Heli (3)Crete (1)
Hawaii (45)
Oahu (18)Maui (25) Kauai (2)
Italy (154)
Florence (6)Sardinia (21)Amalfi Coast (46)Tuscany (38)Siena (14)Forte De Marmi (2)Capri (1)Sorrento Coast (2)Positano (1)Amalfi/Maiori/Ravello (1)Sicily (4)Arezzo and nearby (3)Siena area (3)Umbria (3)Lazio (1)Liguria (3)Lake Como (3)Puglia (1)Rome (1)
Japan (1)
Mt Yotei (1)
Maldives (17)
Maldives (17)
Mauritius (6)
Poste Lafayette (1)Roches Noire (4)Mauritius East (1)
Mexico (47)
Puerto Vallarta (8)Punta Mita (7)Cabo San Lucas (3)Cancun (4)Sian Kaan (3)Puerto Aventuras (9)Akumal (4)Tulum (8)Playa Del Carmen (1)
New Zealand (98)
Queenstown (36)Wanaka (11)Auckland (8)Bay Of Islands (12)Taupo (5)Coromandel (2)Waiheke Island (21)Hawkes Bay (2)Northland (1)
Seychelles (26)
Private Island (7)Mahe (11)Praslin (8)
Spain (3)
Ibiza (3)
Sri Lanka (67)
Sri Lanka (4)Galle (13)Tangalle (7)Habaraduwa-Koggala (15)Galle Fort (9)Dikwella (9)Weligama (1)Kabalana (1)Mirissa (4)Hikkaduwa (1)Colombo (1)Ambalangoda (1)Nuwara Eliya (1)
Tahiti (4)
Bora Bora (1)Mo'orea (3)
USA (18)
Los Angeles (11)Miami (7)
Vietnam (7)
Ha My Beach (1)Vung Tau (3)Ke Ga Bay (1)Cam Ranh (2)
Blog
Contact Us
Favorites 0
Inquire about these villas
Home
Privacy Policy
Welcome to Villa Getaways
— Luxury Villa Rentals Worldwide —
Privacy Policy
Villa Getaways takes your privacy seriously. We make it our highest priority to secure and protect the confidentiality of the personal information that you provide to us.
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
Villa Getaways
P.O. Box 52 Whangamata, New Zealand
sales@villagetaways.com
Our Policies
We collect e-mail addresses and of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by our guests and visitors, such as contact information, survey information and/or site registrations.
The information we collect is used by Villa Getaways to contact our guest and visitors regarding villa rental availability requests they have placed online. We will only send you e-mail or mailings to inform you of updates and product information on Villa Getaways, if you have provided your e-mail address or mailing address to us through our website. Should you wish to opt out of receiving communications from Villa Getaways in the future, please let us know by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link within the e-mail that you received from us, by visiting the our website and clicking the “unsubscribe” button on the homepage, by sending us e-mail at the above address, or by writing to us at the above address. Please allow four to six weeks for the suppression of your name from our lists to become effective.
We do not sell or rent this information to anyone. Villa Getaways will only share your personally identifiable information with our authorized villa service providers that perform certain services or functions on our behalf.
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights.
Updates to our policy
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
External Links
This Web site may provide links to external Web sites maintained by individuals or organizations external to VillaGetaways.com. Once you access information that links you to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of these external sites.
×
Hello world!
OK
